

### LATIFAH ALSUBAIE

# FULL-STACK WEB DEVELOPER

#### <hl>Hello world!</hl>

I am a Full-stack Web Developer graduated from a 1year intensive training in Full-stack Web Development, MERN Stack, Project Manager, and Class Representative.

Seeking a position to apply experience in full-stack as well as deepening and broadening my knowledge in back-end and deliver solution-oriented approaches.

#### SKILLS

Technologies: JavaScript Framework:

Javascript React
Typescript React Native
Html5 Node.js
CSS jQuery

Database: Version Control:

MongoDB G MySQL

Tools: Cloud-Hosted Platform:

Expo Github Android emulator

Jira
Figma
Excalidraw
Canva
Trello
Project Management
Problem Solver

#### LANGUAGES

**Arabic:** Mother tongue

**English:** Full professional proficiency **German:** Professional working proficiency (B2)

#### HOBBIES



#### CONTACT

Location: Wegberg, NRW
Email: latifah4ezohomail.eu
Call/WhatsApp: +49 176 84119444



#### **EDUCATION**

## FULLSTACK WEB DEVELOPMENT DCI Digital Career Institute gGmbH | 2021-2022

- One-year-full-time Full-stack web development and MERN stack training.
- Completed multiple small tasks, SPA final project, and Full-stack final project.
- Lessons in the German language as part of the course with a certificate in level B2

#### **URBAN AGRICULTURE AND GREEN TECHNOLOGY**

#### Brooklyn Grange, NYC | 2017

- Planting and harvesting organic vegetables, fruits, and berries.
- Bee keeping and honey harvesting.
- Micro planting.
- Caring for and supporting plants.

## BACHELOR IN ENGLISH LANGUAGE AND TRANSLATION king Saud University, Riyadh, Saudi Arabia | 2015

- Translation in many different fields.
- Simultaneous and bilateral interpreting English-Arabic &/ Arabic-English.
- Computer applications.
- Comparative cultures.

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

#### **FACTORY-ASSISTANT**

#### Conrad Schulte GmbH, Mastholte | 2018-2020

- Packing backed cookies and taking pallets to the warehouse.
- Preparing machines and resolving the errors.
- Helping in the bakery.

#### HARVEST WORKER

#### Brooklyn Grange, NYC 2016-2017

- Planting and harvesting organic vegetables, fruits, and berries.
- Bee keeping and honey harvesting.
- Micro planting.
- Caring for and supporting plants.